Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series XVIII. Trinkets
  - Silver Elephant Pin "'52", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0014; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "'52 G.O.P.", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0015; Items: 6 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins, Blank, n/a; 6477.TK0016; Items: 111 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "1954", 1954; 6477.TK0017; Items: 5 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Kansas", n/a; 6477.TK0018; Items: 8 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins, Blank, n/a; 6477.TK0019; Items: 2 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Ike Texas", ca. 1952-1956; 6477.TK0020; Items: 4 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "'53", 1953; 6477.TK0021; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "'64", 1964; 6477.TK0022; Items: 7 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Conn '56", 1956; 6477.TK0023; Items: 23 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Washoe GOP 1956"(in small type), 1956; 6477.TK0024; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "Washoe GOP 1956" (in large type), 1956; 6477.TK0025; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Texas '56", 1956; 6477.TK0026; Items: 16 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "'56", 1956; 6477.TK0027; Items: 26 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "'58", 1958; 6477.TK0028; Items: 21 (Box 12)
    Election: 1958
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Ohio", n/a; 6477.TK0029; Items: 15 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Washoe GOP 1955", n/a; 6477.TK0030; Items: 2 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "Washoe GOP 1956", n/a; 6477.TK0031; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Joe Talbot", n/a; 6477.TK0032; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Large Gold Elephant Pin stamped "Joe Talbot", n/a; 6477.TK0033; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Ike", 1952-1956; 6477.TK0034; Items: 7 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "G.O.P.", n/a; 6477.TK0035; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Large Gold Elephant Pin: white blanket lettered "Sherry", n/a; 6477.TK0036; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Large Gold Elephant Pins: "'56" on blue blanket, 1956; 6477.TK0037; Items: 2 (Box 12)
  - Large Gold Elephant Pin "Ken Bradley", n/a; 6477.TK0038; Items: 1 (Box 12)
    Candidate: Bradley, Kenneth
  - Gold Elephant Pins "S.D. G.O.P.", n/a; 6477.TK0039; Items: 6 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "Nevada", n/a; 6477.TK0040; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Heavy Gold Elephant Pins "Taft", n/a; 6477.TK0041; Items: 4 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Taft", n/a; 6477.TK0042; Items: 2 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pin "Taft", n/a; 6477.TK0043; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "Taft in '52", 1952; 6477.TK0044; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Gore", n/a; 6477.TK0045; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "Gore" in raised letters, n/a; 6477.TK0046; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Large Gold Elephant Pin Blank, n/a; 6477.TK0047; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Baker", ca. 1980; 6477.TK0048; Items: 3 (Box 12)
    Candidate: Baker, Howard H. Jr.
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Rocky", ca. 1964-1968; 6477.TK0049; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "Gregg", n/a; 6477.TK0050; Items: 1 (Box 12)
    Candidate: Gregg
  - Gold Elephant Pins "Mechem '52", 1952; 6477.TK0051; Items: 10 (Box 12)
    Candidate: Mechem
  - Large Gold elephant Pin "'52", 1952; 6477.TK0052; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Earring, n/a; 6477.TK0053; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "N.D. G.O.P.", n/a; 6477.TK0054; Items: 2 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "1855 1955", n/a; 6477.TK0055; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "I Like Ike", ca. 1952-1956; 6477.TK0056; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "G.O.P.", n/a; 6477.TK0057; Items: 2 (Box 13)
  - Copper Elephant Pin "G.O.P.", n/a; 6477.TK0058; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "G.O.P." in small letters, n/a; 6477.TK0059; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "G.O.P." in large letters, n/a; 6477.TK0060; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "G.O.P." in large raised letters, n/a; 6477.TK0061; Items: 3 (Box 13)
  - Gold Running Elephant Pins "G.O.P." in large raised letters, n/a; 6477.TK0062; Items: 10 (Box 13)
  - Gold Donkey Pins, n/a; 6477.TK0063; Items: 2 (Box 13)
  - Gold Donkey Pins "1956" in large raised numbers, 1956; 6477.TK0064; Items: 20 (Box 13)
  - Silver Donkey Pins "1956" in large raised numbers, 1956; 6477.TK0065; Items: 4 (Box 13)
  - Gold Donkey Pin "1962" in large raised numbers, 1962; 6477.TK0066; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Gold Donkey Pin "L B J", ca. 1964; 6477.TK0067; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Silver Elephant Pin, n/a; 6477.TK0068; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Tarnished Elephant Pins "Lodge", ca. 1964; 6477.TK0069; Items: 2 (Box 13)
    Candidate: Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr.
  - "Kennedy '64" Gold Massachusetts-Shaped Pin, 1964; 6477.TK0070; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - "Kennedy-Johnson USA" Donkey In Top-Hat Pin, ca. 1960; 6477.TK0071; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - "Adlai" Pin, ca. 1952-1956; 6477.TK0072; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Red White & Blue Metal Rosette Pin "Roosevelt", ca. 1932-1944; 6477.TK0073; Items: 1 (Box 13)
    Election: 1932; 1936; 1940; 1944
  - "NRA Member U.S. We Do Our Part" Tie Tack, n/a; 6477.TK0074; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - "Fiorello LaGuardia Mayor Of N.Y.C. Nov 7 1933" Medal, 1933; 6477.TK0075; Items: 1 (Box 13)
    Candidate: LaGuardia, Fiorello H.
    Election: 1933
  - LBJ Charm/Medalion, ca. 1964; 6477.TK0076; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - LBJ Pin, ca. 1964; 6477.TK0077; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Peanut Necklaces, one gold, 6477.TK0078; Items: 4 (Box 26)
- Series XIX. Wearing Apparel
  - HHH Tie Clip, ca. 1968; 6477.WA0001; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - Nixon Tie Clip, ca. 1960;1968;1972; 6477.WA0002; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - "I Like Ike" Necktie, ca. 1952-1956; 6477.WA0003; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Humphrey-Muskie Bracelet, ca. 1968; 6477.WA0004; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - "Sen. Kennedy" Tie Clip, ca. 1960; 6477.WA0005; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - Republican National Convention Cuff Link, 1972; 6477.WA0006; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - McHugh For Congress Tee Shirt, ca. 1976; 6477.WA0007; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: McHugh Matthew
  - Kerry/Edwards/The Race for the White House 2004 Tee Shirt, 2004; 6477.WA0008; Items: 1 (Box 22)
  - Independent/Ross Perot/President Tee Shirt, 1992 or 1996; 6477.WA0009; Items: 1 (Box 22)
  - Mr. Flip Flop Sandals, 2004; 6477.WA0010; Items: 1 (Box 22)
  - Presidential Inauguration Tee shirts from Washington, D.C., 2017; 6477.WA0011-13; Items: 3 (Box 29)
  - Obama "Made America Great Again" Tee shirt, 2016; 6477.WA0014; Items: 1 (Box 29)
- Series XX. Sound Recordings
  - Presidential Campaign Songs 1789-1996 sung by Oscar Brand, 1999; 6477.CD-498; Items: 1 (Box 20)